Dive
沉醉于此
歌手：Usher
压制:随Feng
I know you think I'm afraid
我知道你害怕我
To take a chance
拥有了一次机会
Go to the deep end
将会堕入深渊
Usher baby
亚瑟小子
Turn the lights off
关闭灯光
These waters can get a little busy
水涨的有些急促
But I got experience
但我深识水性
Don't mind trecking to the storm
别只想着翻腾弄海
Long as I know that you're here with me baby
宝贝 只要知道你在我身边就好
Shedding all your innocence
流露出你的纯情
I see the walls are looking like they might precipitate
我看到 那堵心墙似乎倾刻会倒塌
Until i'm in so deep, it's up to my ways
深入内部 唯我所欲
But I promise girl I ain't afraid
我保证 勇者无惧
It's raining inside your bed
你的爱窝里 雨落连绵
No buts, or dry
没有一丝干涸
Love makes you so wet, your legs, your thighs
爱抚令你遍地滋润
And ever since we first met I knew that
从初次相见起 我就知道
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
我已经准备好了 我将潜入深潮
Can't help it, no
欲罢不能
I want you to feel me
想让你感受我的身体
Every little bit of me
我的每一寸肌肤
I don't need a life saver
我不需要救生圈
Baby going deeper ain't gon kill me
宝贝 再深一点 我不会有事
And I know they are shagging for me
潮水之中 相交甚欢
I see the walls are looking like they might precipitate
我看到 那堵心墙似乎倾刻会倒塌
Until i'm in so deep, it's up to my ways
深入内部 唯我所欲
But I promise girl I ain't afraid
我保证 勇者无惧
It's raining inside your bed
你的爱窝里 雨落连绵
No buts, or dry
没有一丝干涸
Love makes you so wet, your legs, your thighs
爱抚令你遍地滋润
And ever since we first met I knew that
从初次相见起 我就知道
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
我已经准备好了 我将潜入深潮
I'll be inside when the tides are rolling baby
潮水翻滚 我顺水推舟
You'll be my place tonight, all night
今夜 你是我整夜的归宿
I'm not afraid to try
我不怕一试
And knew i, don't mind playing in the rain
我不介意 在你的绵雨中玩肆
And I was hoping that I get to take that dive
我希望我能 潜入你的深潮
It's raining inside your bed
你的爱窝里 雨落连绵
No buts, or dry
没有一丝干涸
Love makes you so wet, your legs, your thighs
爱抚让你遍地滋润
And ever since we first met I knew that
从初次见面 我就知道
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
我已经准备好了 我将潜入你的深潮
压制:随Feng